(this.webpackJsonpquizzap=this.webpackJsonpquizzap||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,c){"use strict";c.r(t);var a=c(0),r=c.n(a),n=c(3),o=c.n(n),i=(c(9),c(1));var l=function(e){return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Instructions"),r.a.createElement("p",null,"Choose the best answer from the choices. To pass, you must get a score of at least 80%."),r.a.createElement("p",null,"You can always go back to the previous questions to review your answers. When you are done, click ",r.a.createElement("strong",null,"Submit"),"."),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"next",onClick:e.handleStartQuiz},"Start Quiz"))},u=[{question:"When 1100010 is divided by 0101, what will be the decimal remainder?",a:{choice:"2",correct:!1},b:{choice:"3",correct:!0},c:{choice:"4",correct:!1},d:{choice:"6",correct:!1}},{question:"A logic circuit that provides a HIGH output for both inputs HIGH or both inputs LOW is a(n):",a:{choice:"Ex-NOR gate",correct:!0},b:{choice:"OR gate",correct:!1},c:{choice:"Ex-OR gate",correct:!1},d:{choice:"NAND gate",correct:!1}},{question:"Identify the type of gate from the equation X = A'B + AB'",a:{choice:"Ex-NOR gate",correct:!1},b:{choice:"OR gate",correct:!1},c:{choice:"Ex-OR gate",correct:!0},d:{choice:"NAND gate",correct:!1}},{question:"How many basic binary subtraction operations are possible?",a:{choice:"4",correct:!1},b:{choice:"3",correct:!1},c:{choice:"2",correct:!1},d:{choice:"1",correct:!0}},{question:"Parity systems are defined as either________ or ________ and will add an extra ________ to the digital information being transmitted.",a:{choice:"positive, negative, byte",correct:!1},b:{choice:"odd, even, bit",correct:!0},c:{choice:"upper, lower, digit",correct:!1},d:{choice:"on, off, decimal",correct:!1}},{question:"The bits of a number that tell how large the number is are called ____________________.",a:{choice:"carry bits",correct:!1},b:{choice:"magnitude bits",correct:!0},c:{choice:"sign bits",correct:!1},d:{choice:"most significant bits",correct:!1}},{question:"Which type of gate can be used to add two bits?",a:{choice:"EX-OR",correct:!0},b:{choice:"EX-NOR",correct:!1},c:{choice:"EX-NAND",correct:!1},d:{choice:"NOR",correct:!1}},{question:"In binary number systems the sign of a number is indicated by _________.",a:{choice:"Using a 0 (zero) bit in front of negative numbers",correct:!1},b:{choice:"Inverting the bits if the number is negative",correct:!1},c:{choice:"Including a sign bit along with the magnitude bits",correct:!0},d:{choice:"Placing a negative sign in front of the number",correct:!1}},{question:"Adding in binary, the decimal values 26 + 27 will produce a sum of:",a:{choice:"111010",correct:!1},b:{choice:"110110",correct:!1},c:{choice:"110101",correct:!0},d:{choice:"101011",correct:!1}},{question:"The Ex-NOR is sometimes called the ________.",a:{choice:"Parity Gate",correct:!1},b:{choice:"Equality Gate",correct:!0},c:{choice:"Inverted OR",correct:!1},d:{choice:"Parity Gate or the Equality Gate",correct:!1}}];var s=function(e){var t=Object(a.useState)(0),c=Object(i.a)(t,2),n=c[0],o=c[1],l=Object(a.useState)(u[n]),s=Object(i.a)(l,2),h=s[0],m=s[1],d=Object(a.useState)(null),b=Object(i.a)(d,2),g=b[0],_=b[1];function E(e){_(e.target.value)}return r.a.createElement("form",null,r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Question #",n+1),r.a.createElement("p",null,h.question),r.a.createElement("ul",{className:"choicesContainer"},r.a.createElement("li",null,r.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",name:"choice",value:"a",checked:"a"===g,onChange:E,id:"a"}),r.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"a"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceLetter"},"A"),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceText"},h.a.choice))),r.a.createElement("li",null,r.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",name:"choice",value:"b",checked:"b"===g,onChange:E,id:"b"}),r.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"b"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceLetter"},"B"),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceText"},h.b.choice))),r.a.createElement("li",null,r.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",name:"choice",value:"c",checked:"c"===g,onChange:E,id:"c"}),r.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"c"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceLetter"},"C"),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceText"},h.c.choice))),r.a.createElement("li",null,r.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",name:"choice",value:"d",checked:"d"===g,onChange:E,id:"d"}),r.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"d"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceLetter"},"D"),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"choiceText"},h.d.choice)))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"buttonContainer"},0!==n?r.a.createElement("button",{className:"prev",onClick:function(e){e.preventDefault(),o((function(e){return e-1})),m(u[n-1]);var t=localStorage.getItem(n-1);_(t)}},"Prev"):null,n+1===u.length?r.a.createElement("button",{className:"submit",onClick:function(t){t.preventDefault(),localStorage.setItem(n,g),e.handleResult()}},"Submit"):r.a.createElement("button",{className:"next",onClick:function(e){if(e.preventDefault(),o((function(e){return e+1})),m(u[n+1]),localStorage.setItem(n,g),null===localStorage.getItem(n))_("");else{var t=localStorage.getItem(n+1);_(t)}}},"Next")))};var h=function(e){function t(){for(var e=0,t=0;t<u.length;t++)"null"!==localStorage.getItem(t.toString())&&u[t][localStorage.getItem(t)].correct&&e++;return e}return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"resultsContainer"},r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Results"),r.a.createElement("p",null,"Your result is"),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"score"},t(),"/",u.length),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"result"},t()>=.8*u.length?"You Passed!":"You Failed."),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"tryAgain",onClick:e.handleIntro},"Try Again"))};var m=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)(!1),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),c=t[0],n=t[1],o=Object(a.useState)(!0),u=Object(i.a)(o,2),m=u[0],d=u[1],b=Object(a.useState)(!1),g=Object(i.a)(b,2),_=g[0],E=g[1];return r.a.createElement("div",null,m&&r.a.createElement(l,{handleStartQuiz:function(){n((function(e){return!e})),d((function(e){return!e})),localStorage.clear()}}),c&&r.a.createElement(s,{handleResult:function(){n((function(e){return!e})),E((function(e){return!e}))}}),_&&r.a.createElement(h,{handleIntro:function(){E((function(e){return!e})),d((function(e){return!e})),localStorage.clear()}}))};o.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(m,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,t,c){e.exports=c(10)},9:function(e,t,c){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.e13d2d7e.chunk.js.map